Now watch, they gave him a chance to say the right thing, and well...
We'll work as hard as I can to get the Biden administration to support.
The UN tried to bring about a ceasefire, a humanitarian cause ceasefire,
in order to provide the gestures that needed aid that they caused on people.
When you get to the world, I get a little bit queasy.
It is a genocide!
What's your definition of genocide?
Bernie, you have funded Zionism yourself.
You have funded the Israeli settler state.
Here you are, pretending you aren't.
It is disgusting! Liar, liar, genocide, denier!
Liar, liar, genocide, denier!
It's disgusting!
And it's reprehensible!
You are a child-killer!
You are a genocide-designed liar!
The United States military-industrial complex are the largest murderers in the world.
It does not matter if it is a Democrat or a Republican.
You have murdered people around the world.
The Native Americans are still being genocided.
I have never heard you once speak about genocide.
Bernie done burned himself.
I have never heard you once again.
There's not Minnie finished.
Here we go.
Go for it!
Maybe you're lying!
Let me see!
Anyway, somebody darkerets me.
Come and drink under panic!
I'll get you!
φiza abreast!
Like, please do not love to block you!
Over here our house!
Maybe yes, please do not forget
to let the Noah end up for your world you don't have to.